&gt;&gt; Some of the most important recent breakthroughs in the performance of self-driving cars,
&gt;&gt; 自動運転車の性能に 見られる 最近の 飛躍的進歩の中には
have come from machine learning.
マシーンラーニングによるものが あります
Two of my Udacity colleagues,
Udacityの同僚である
Luis and Mat, are machine learning experts.
LuisとMatは マシーンラーニングの 専門家です
In this lesson, they're going to introduce you to
このレッスンでは 2人に マシーンラーニング分野の
the foundational concepts in the fields of machine learning and deep neural networks.
基礎的な概念と 深層ニューラルネットワークを 紹介してもらいます
Afterward, we'll build on those concepts and apply them to self-driving cars.
その後 それらの概念を 発展させ 自動運転車に 当てはめてみたいと思います
&gt;&gt; Hi, I'm Louis Serrano,
&gt;&gt; こんにちは Louis Serranoです
and I lead the Machine Learning Nanodegree program at Udacity.
Udacityの マシーンラーニングNanodegreeプログラム 主任です
Machine learning is a field of artificial intelligence that relies
マシーンラーニングは 人工知能の 一分野で
on computers to learn about the environment from data,
コンピューターを利用し データから 環境について学習します
instead of relying on the rule set by computer programmers.
プログラマーによって 設定された ルールに 頼るのではありません
&gt;&gt; And I'm Mat Leonard,
&gt;&gt; こんにちは Mat Leonardです
I lead the Deep Learning Nanodegree Foundation program.
ディープラーニングNanodegree基礎プログラムの 主任です
Deep learning is an approach to machine learning,
ディープラーニングは マシーンラーニングへの アプローチの1つで
that uses deep neural networks.
深層ニューラルネットワークを 利用します
Deep learning uses this one tool to accomplish an amazing array of objectives,
ディープラーニングは この1つのツールだけで 音声認識から 自動運転まで
from speech recognition, to driving a car.
驚くほど さまざまな目的を 達成します
&gt;&gt; You'll start learning about the perceptron,
&gt;&gt; ここでは ニューラルネットワークの
which is the fundamental unit of a neural network.
基本単位である パーセプトロンから 紹介していきます
&gt;&gt; Then you'll learn how to combine these units into a simple neural network.
&gt;&gt; 続いて それを組み合わせ 単純なニューラルネットワークを 構築する方法を 学びます
&gt;&gt; Before you start learning about neural network though,
&gt;&gt; では ニューラルネットワークの前に
let's go over the basics of machine learning.
マシーンラーニングの基礎を おさらいしましょう
We'll get started by thinking about something a little less
まずは 自動運転車より ちょっと単純な
complex than self-driving cars. Housing prices.
ものについて 考えます住宅の価格です